ILR School Librarian's Office Files /4004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- American Arbitration Association Requisitions, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- American Civil Liberties Requisitions, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- American Library Association Requisitions, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- American Management Association Requisitions, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- American Trucking Associations, Inc. Requisitions, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- B General, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Bernan Associates, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Bibliographic Retrieval Services Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- British Association for Commercial and Industrial Education, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Bureau of National Affairs April 1960- (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Canada Law Book, LTD. Requisitions, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Commerce Clearing House Requisitions, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Committee for Economic Development Requisitions, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- The Conference Board Requisitions, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Congressional Information Service, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- The Cornell Daily Sun, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Cornell University - Acquisitions Libraries (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Cornell University - General, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- C.U. Libraries, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Cornell University Libraries Supplies, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Cornell University - Stores Billing (Box 34, Folder 25)
- D General, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- The Daily World Requisitions, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Dun and Bradstreet, Inc., 1979 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- EBSCO Subscription Service, 1977-1979 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Elliot Service Company, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Executive Enterprises Pub., Co., 1979 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Gale Research Company, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Gaylord Brothers, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- H General, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- I General, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Incomes Data Services Ltd., 1974 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Industrial Relations Research Association, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Information Bank, 1978-1981 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Interdepartmental Orders, 1982-1985 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Interdepartmental Orders, 1981-1983 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Interdepartmental Orders - Communications, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Interdepartmental Orders - Communication, 1980-1981 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Interdepartmental Orders Communications, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Interdepartmental Orders - Credits, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- "J" General, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- "L" General, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Labor Relations Associations, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Labor Research Association, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Labor Relations Press, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Lockheed Missiles and Space Co. Dialog Information Service, 1978-1981 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- "M" General, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Massachusetts Labor Relations Reporter, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Microfilming Corporation of America, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- "A" General, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- "B" General, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- BRS, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- BNA, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- "C" General, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Cornell General (Box 36, Folder 6)
- "D" General, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Dartnell Corporation Requisitions, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Dialog Info. Srcs., 1982 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- "E" General, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- "F" General, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- "G" General, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- "H" General, 1981-1983 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- IBM Corp., 1950 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- International Labor Office, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- "L" General, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Labor Relations Press (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Legislative Index Company Requisitions, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- "M" General, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Microfilming Corporation of America Requisitions, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Moody's Investors Service Requisitions, 1957 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Moody's Investor Service Requisitions, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- "N" General, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- National Education Association, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- National Mediation Board, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- New York Times The Information Bank Requisitions, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Nichols Business Equipment Inc., 1976 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- "O" General, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Opinions Press Requisitions, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- "P" General, 1970-1979 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Personnel Management Abstracts Requisitions, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Prentice-Hall, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Preventive Labor Relations Requisitions, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Public Affairs Information Service Requisitions, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Systems, Ltd. Requisitions, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- "R" General, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- "S" General, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Shepard's, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Social Legislation Information Service Requisitions, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Sociological Abstracts, Inc. Requisitions, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 24)
- The Source, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Special Libraries Association Requisitions, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Charles D. Spencer, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Mark A. Stephens, Ltd. Requisitions, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Student Newspaper Agency July 1960- (Box 37, Folder 29)
- System Development Corporation, 1978-1981 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- "T" General, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 31)
- Transcribers-Neh Grant Requisitions, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- NYSSILR B-10.5 Travel Expense Accounts 1979- (Box 37, Folder 33)
- NYSSILR B-10.5 Travel Expense Accounts 1979- (Box 37, Folder 33)